<resources>
    <!-- Title for the application. [CHAR LIMIT=30] -->
    <string name="app_name">Trinidad &amp; Tobago Tour Guide</string>
    <!-- Category name for Best Beaches in Trinidad & Tobago [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_beaches">Beaches</string>

    <!-- Category name for Best Restaurants in Trinidad & Tobago[CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_dining">Dining</string>

    <!-- Category name for Events in Trinidad & Tobago [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_events">Events</string>

    <!-- Category name for Best Resorts in Trinidad & Tobago [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_resorts">Resorts</string>

    <string name="beaches_one">
        LAS CUEVAS\n\n
        Experience an authentic and unspoiled Caribbean beach in a half-day trip to Las Cuevas Beach from Port of Spain.\n
This 1.36-mile (2.2-kilometer) beach is a Blue Flag award winner for its purity and compliance to international standards.\n
Highlights of the tour include a Maracas Lookout photo op, a North Coast Road scenic drive, and a chance to sample local
delicacies (own expense), such as sesame seed balls and pineapple chutney.\n
North Coast Road, Trinidad.
    </string>
    <string name="beaches_two">
        MARACAS BAY\n\n
Maracas Beach is the most popular beach in the North of Trinidad. \n
The drive to Maracas is spectacular, looking at scenic mountain views
and breathtaking views of the beach and the Caribbean Sea.\n
Once at the beach you can surf, take a swim or just simply sunbathe\n
and have a great time under the palm trees. \n
The most popular activity on the beach is tasting the world famous "bake and shark." \n
Located at the North Coast of Trinidad.
    </string>
    <string name="beaches_three">
        PIGEON POINT\n\n
Pigeon Point is also known as Pigeon Point Heritage Park and is often considered
Tobago\'s most beautiful beach and is home to the world famous thatch-roofed jetty
which has become an internationally recognised signature of Tobago. \n
The resort includes a long stretch of white sand beach with warm aquamarine waters
Located at Crown Point which is South-West in Tobago.
    </string>
    <string name="beaches_four">
        STORE BAY\n\n
Just a 5-minute walk from the airport, this 200m stretch of sand meets surf,
is one of Tobago\'s most popular beaches for visitors and locals alike. \n
Known for its crystal clear waters, sunny days, and the laid-back island vibe,
Store Bay makes for a perfect getaway from your hectic everyday. \n
Located at Crown Point, South West in Tobago
    </string>
    <string name="dining_one">
        CHAUD\n\n
Food is superb. Every dish is exciting and very tasty. \n
Service was also impeccable. The desserts were delicious \n
and very artistic\n
6 Nook Avenue, St. Anns, Port-Of-Spain, Trinidad.\n
1-(868)-621-2002
    </string>
    <string name="dining_two">
        JAFFA AT THE OVAL\n\n
Sumptuous buffet lunch for excellent value at a premier location,
the Trinidad Oval! \n
        Serve an excellent selection of authentic Trini
dishes as well as other traditional fare. Convenient parking.\n
94 Tragarete Road, Queen's Park Oval, Port-Of-Spain, Trinidad.\n
1-(868)-628-6200
    </string>
    <string name="dining_three">
        KARIWAK VILLAGE\n\n
Offers a winning combination of excellent Creole-style food and friendly service.\n
Prix fixe and a la carte menus are available for breakfast, lunch and dinner. \n
The real treat is that many of Kariwak’s dishes are accented with freshly picked
herbs and vegetables pulled from its garden.\n
Store Bay Local Road, Kariwak Village Street, Crown Point, Tobago\n
1-(868)-639-8442
    </string>
    <string name="dining_four">
        SEAHORSE INN\n\n
From Seafood to Steaks, Creole &amp; International style cuisine. Nightly Entertainment. \n
Enjoy cocktails with a magnificent sunset. Dine under the stars. \n
Be caressed by the sound of the surf and the breeze in the coconut trees. \n
Old Grafton Beach Road, Tobago \n
1-(868)-639-0686
    </string>
    <string name="events_one">
        SANTA ROSA CARIB FESTIVAL\n\n
The Santa Rosa Carib Festival takes place in August during the week
leading up to T&amp;T Independence Day, Aug. 31, and honors the indigenous
First Peoples who populated Trinidad and Tobago for thousands of years
before European settlement.\n
        Highlights include the crowning of a Carib
Queen, a church procession, and performance of traditional music and
ritual smoke ceremonies and prayer.
    </string>
    <string name="events_two">
        TOBAGO HERITAGE FESTIVAL\n\n
The annual Tobago Heritage Festival starts in mid-July
and peaks on Emancipation Day, Aug. 1, with a Carnival-style
j\'ouvert celebration. The festival focuses mainly on African music,
dance and traditions, including a traditional (mock) old-fashioned
wedding ceremony in the village of Moriah that honors the melding of
African and European traditions.
    </string>
    <string name="events_three">
        TRINDAD CARNIVAL\n\n
The Trinidad and Tobago Carnival is an annual event held on the Monday and Tuesday
before Ash Wednesday in Trinidad and Tobago. The event is well known for participants\'
colorful costumes and exuberant celebrations.
    </string>
    <string name="events_four">
        PANORAMA\n\n
Annual music competition held during Carnival. \n
The preliminary round takes place in the respective panyards
while the other rounds are held at the Queens Park Savannah,
Port of Spain, fondly called the ‘Big Yard’.\n\n
There are four main steelband categories in the Panorama competition.\n
Large Conventional Steelbands - minimum of 95 and a maximum of 120 players.\n
Medium Conventional Steelbands - minimum of 60 and a maximum of 90 players.\n
Small Conventional Steelbands - minimum of 35 and a maximum of 55 players.\n
Single Pan Bands - minimum of 25 and a maximum of 45 players.\n
Conventional bands play an arrangement of a calypso for a maximum of 8 minutes.\n
Single pan bands (which are harder to arrange for) play an arrangement of a calypso for a maximum of six minutes.\n
Points are awarded for: Arrangement, General Performance, Tone and Rhythm
    </string>
    <string name="resorts_one">
        COCO REEF RESORT\n\n
Coco Reef is Tobago\'s premier beachfront hotel, sitting on ten acres
of manicured tropical gardens. It provides the ultimate Caribbean
vacation in a casually elegant setting.\n
Coco Reef\'s guest accommodations feature tropical elegance with saltillo
tiled patios and balconies, exquisite wall stencils, tiled vanities and the
very finest hand-crafted wicker furniture. Of Coco Reef\'s total of 135 rooms,
suites and villas, 114 have ocean views.\n
        Coconut Bay, Bon Accord Village, Crown Point, Tobago\n
        i-(868)-639-8571
    </string>
    <string name="resorts_two">
        GRAFTON BEACH RESORT\n\n
Located on a half mile stretch of sandy beaches and tropical waters in Tobago,
Grafton Beach Resort captures the true essence of a Caribbean vacation with three
stories of relaxing accommodations perfect for a the whole family or a romantic getaway.\n
Shirvan Road, Black Rock, Tobago \n
1-(868)-639-0191 \n
    </string>
    <string name="resorts_three">
        HILTON RESORT\n\n
Located on a hilltop overlooking the iconic Queen\'s Park Savannah,
th hotel offers Guests an ideal location, spacious accommodations and
breathtaking views of the city of Port of Spain as well as the Northern Range mountains.\n
Beautiful Caribbean surroundings give Guests a truly unique Caribbean experience
just minutes away from the busy city centre.\n
Local nearby sights include Royal Botanical Gardens and Emperor Valley Zoo.\n
Lady Young Road, Port-Of-Spain, Trinidad.\n
1-(868)-624-3211
    </string>
    <string name="resorts_four">
        HYATT HOTEL\n\n
The Hyatt Regency Trinidad offers elegantly appointed guestrooms for idyllic
timeshare vacations in Port of Spain, Trinidad. Hyatt\'s Grand Beds, iPod docking
stations, flat screen TVs, and bamboo flooring are among the features of the
accommodations awaiting you at the Hyatt Regency Trinidad!\n
Amenities at the Hyatt Regency Trinidad do not disappoint! \n 
Look forward to a rooftop infinity pool, a full service spa,
24 hour room service, dining venues ranging from gourmet fare
to quick meals, a sun deck, and more!\n
        In true Hyatt style, you\'ll
have the assistance of personal shoppers and a concierge!\n
#1 Winston Road, Port-Of_Spain, Trinidad.\n
1-(868)-623-2222
    </string>
</resources>
